so I think the flow people are slowed
所以我觉得人流慢了
down so we'll get started
下来，所以我们开始
so welcome this is jump and start your
因此，欢迎您跳跃并开始您的
micro service development with Java EE
Java EE开发微服务
I'm Kate Stanley mrs. Graham charters we
我是Kate Stanley夫人。格雷厄姆宪章我们
both work for IBM and we're hopefully
两者都适用于IBM，我们希望
gonna give you some information today
今天要给你一些信息
about why we think Java is a good fit
关于为什么我们认为Java很合适
for micro services so this is the
对于微服务，这就是
content that we're going to talk to you
我们将要与您交谈的内容
about today we'll have a little bit of
大约今天，
an introduction to microservices just a
微服务介绍只是一个
quick show of hands who here already
快速举手的人已经在这里
thinks they know what a micro services
以为他们知道微服务是什么
okay so we'll give a bit of introduction
好的，我们将做一些介绍
then hope for you level set where we are
然后希望为您设置我们所处的水平
and then we're going to talk about Java
然后我们将讨论Java
EE evolution some stuff about docker and
EE Evolution关于docker和
micro services some packaging
微服务一些包装
considerations that you might want to
您可能需要考虑的事项
think about while you're creating
在创建时考虑一下
applications and then also how you can
应用程序，然后又如何
use the open API specification and a
使用开放的API规范和
conclusion we're going to show a couple
结论我们将展示几个
of demos as well we'll try and keep the
的演示以及我们将尽力保持
talk quite general about Java EE but
关于Java EE的讨论颇为笼统
because we both work for IBM we're going
因为我们俩都在为IBM工作，所以我们要
to kind of demo the things that we know
演示我们知道的事情
and we're used to and hope that the demo
我们习惯了并希望演示
gods smile on us today so let's get
众神今天对我们微笑，让我们开始吧
started
开始了
so what are micro services they're used
那么它们使用的微服务是什么
to compose a complex application using
组成一个复杂的应用程序使用
small independent autonomous replaceable
小型独立自主可更换
processes that communicate via language
通过语言交流的过程
agnostic api's so rather than deploying
不可知的api而不是部署
one big application you deploy it in
您将其部署到一个大应用程序中
lots of small pieces and they come with
很多小块，他们来了
some advantages and then some sort of
一些优势，然后是某种
complexities and difficulties at the
的复杂性和困难
same time so whenever I'm giving a
同时，所以每当我给
microsomes talk I always kind of say go
微粒子的谈话我总是会说走
have a look read don't just choose micro
看一看不只是选择微
services because you think it's going to
服务，因为您认为这将
solve all your problems because it does
解决您所有的问题，因为它确实
have some added complexity so some of
有一些额外的复杂性，所以一些
the advantages are that you can scale
优点是您可以扩展
your applications in individual pieces
您的应用程序是单独的
you can deploy new versions of the micro
您可以部署微型新版本
services very quickly but then it comes
服务很快，但是后来
from some with some disadvantages of
从某些缺点
having
有
flexitarian how those services interact
弹性主义者，这些服务如何相互作用
and how they call each other the other
以及他们如何互相称呼
thing that's worth mentioning around
值得一提的事情
microservices is twelve faxes so twelve
微服务是十二个传真，所以十二个
factors is a methodology for building
因素是一种构建方法
software as a service applications it
软件即服务应用程序
was created by the developers at Heroku
由Heroku的开发人员创建
and although I wouldn't say that you
虽然我不会说你
have to follow all of these factors if
必须遵循所有这些因素，如果
you want to build a successful micro
你想建立一个成功的微型
service it definitely is a good starting
服务绝对是一个好的开始
point to get you thinking and having
指向让您思考和拥有
your head in the right space so I've
你的头在正确的空间，所以我
listed them all there I'm not going to
列出所有我不会去的地方
go into detail today on all of them but
今天就对它们全部进行详细介绍，
you can go to twelve factor net and read
你可以去十二因子网阅读
about the different factors but if you
关于不同的因素，但是如果你
keep these in mind while you're building
在构建时记住这些
micro services then you'll find that
微服务，那么您会发现
your applications are better suited for
您的应用程序更适合
the cloud and better suited for the kind
云，更适合那种
of environments that you want micro
您想要的微环境
services for so what should we look for
服务，所以我们应该寻找什么
in a micro service environment so this
在微服务环境中
is not just the twelve factors but a
不仅是十二个因素，而且
little bit beyond as well so obviously
一点点也是如此明显
some micro service technologies you
您一些微服务技术
might want to look at how are you going
可能想看看你怎么样
to secure your application one of the
保护您的应用程序之一
other considerations with micro services
微服务的其他考虑
is because of the communication aspect
是因为沟通方面
you need to consider fault tolerance and
您需要考虑容错能力和
what are you going to do if one of your
如果你的一个你打算怎么办
services goes down another thing might
服务下降了另一件事可能
be looking at how you're going to do
在看你打算怎么做
load balancing or how you're going to
负载平衡或您打算如何
find the services in the first place so
首先找到服务
there's some different technologies that
有一些不同的技术
you're going to need to look out for
您将需要注意
when you're trying to decide what you
当你试图决定自己
might need from a micro service
微服务可能需要
environment the next two there come
环境接下来的两个
straight from the twelve factors that's
直接来自十二个因素
fast start up and clean shutdown an
快速启动并彻底关机
individual micro service should be
个别微服务应为
something that you can just throw away
你可以扔掉的东西
and once you throw one away you should
一旦扔掉你应该
be able to start it up again very
能够再次启动它
quickly so you'll hear people saying
快速，所以您会听到人们说
that micro services should be stateless
微服务应该是无状态的
you don't want to have to do some sort
你不想做某种事情
of process where you store some data
您存储一些数据的过程
that was in caching and having to kind
那是在缓存中并且必须友好
of think about that before the
想到之前
application goes down if the application
如果应用程序关闭
goes down you should be able to just
掉下来，你应该能够
start up a new one and carry on the
开始一个新的并继续
movement towards micro services has kind
朝着微服务的方向发展
of come alongside cloud native
与云原生一起
applications and a movement
应用程序和运动
to the cloud so a small footprint is
到云端，因此占用的空间很小
useful here because you're paying for
在这里有用，因为您要付费
the amount of space that you're using
您正在使用的空间量
often and that's where again with micro
经常，那又是微型的地方
services the scaling comes in because
服务扩展，因为
you just want to scale up exactly what
你只想扩大规模
you need and not have to pay for a lot
您需要而不必付出很多
of space and things that you aren't
不属于你的空间和事物
actually using externalising config is
实际使用外部化配置是
something you want to do for
你想做的事情
microservices it again comes from the
微服务再次来自
twelve factors basically means rather
十二个因素基本上意味着
than having your particular application
比拥有您的特定应用程序
have all the detail config for that
具有所有的详细配置
particular environment you want to be
您想要成为的特定环境
able to inject that config so that may
能够注入该配置，以便可能
be through environment variables for
通过环境变量
example and that way you can redeploy
示例，这样您就可以重新部署
your application in many different
您的应用程序有很多不同
environments and you've just changed the
环境，而您刚刚更改了
config that gets injected into the
注入到的配置
application you don't tightly cup all
应用程序您不会紧紧抓住所有
the application with its config the aim
具有配置目的的应用程序
with micro services is to be able to
与微服务是为了能够
iterate faster and get more out of your
迭代得更快，并从中获得更多收益
application and with this comes a need
应用程序，这需要
to be able to make changes and push them
能够做出改变并推动他们
up and a need for developers to be able
和开发人员的能力需求
to actually run what's in development to
实际运行开发中的东西
be the same as what's in production
与生产中的相同
you'll find if your developers doing
您会发现您的开发人员是否在
something completely different from
完全不同于
what's in production then when you try
当您尝试生产什么
to deploy it to production you're going
部署到生产中
to have a problem and that slows down
有一个问题，这会减慢速度
the amount of time between the developer
开发商之间的时间间隔
making the first code change and it
进行第一个代码更改及其
getting out to production and since one
从一开始就投入生产
of the reasons to move to mic receiver
转到麦克风接收器的原因
sees is to speed up that cycle then
看到的是加快那个周期
having development and production parity
具有开发和生产平价
is very important and then the last one
非常重要，然后是最后一个
is containerization we're going to talk
我们要谈的是集装箱化
a bit about the advantages of
关于它的优点
containerization but it's something you
容器化，但这是你的事
might want to consider if you're moving
可能要考虑您是否要搬家
to mic reservist --is
给麦克风后备人员
so it's quite clear I think I've heard
所以很明显我想我已经听过
many people say that because there's a
很多人说，因为有一个
perception that Java is too slow too
Java太慢的看法
bloated and I think it's worth looking
肿，我认为值得一看
back through the kind of history of Java
回顾一下Java的历史
reeds don't understand how we got to
芦苇不明白我们如何去
that perception but then also then I'll
这种感觉，然后我也会
follow on by looking at what some
继续看一些
vendors in the industry are doing to to
行业中的供应商正在努力
kind of move away from this this view
有点偏离这种观点
that Java is is a large bloated slow
Java是个肿的缓慢
environment so if we look back back in
环境，所以如果我们回顾过去
1998 when first Java EE came out it was
1998年，第一个Java EE诞生了
a small number of specifications and a
少量的规格和
small number of technologies and over
少数技术及以上
the years we've added more and more
我们增加了越来越多的岁月
specifications to get to the point where
规格达到点
we where we are today with Java EE 8 and
我们现在使用Java EE 8和
it was quite clear in the kind of 2009
2009年的情况很明显
timeframe that there was a need for
有必要的时间表
something smaller and so we started
一些较小的东西，所以我们开始
creating profiles so for example the web
创建配置文件，例如网络
profile and then Evol platform for all
配置文件，然后为所有Evol平台
the technologies but I think what we've
技术，但我认为我们已经
seen is that you can create a profile so
看到的是您可以创建配置文件
web profile when I talk to customers and
与客户交谈时的网络个人资料，以及
we have we have in our DM offerings that
我们在DM产品中拥有
align with those profiles they say well
与他们说得很好的个人资料保持一致
that's okay I like web profile but I
没关系，我喜欢个人资料，但我
just want this capability or actually I
只是想要这种功能，或者实际上我
don't want all of web profile I just
不想只我所有的网络个人资料
want servlet or servlet and c-d-i and
需要servlet或servlet和cdi以及
things like that so customers are
这样的事情，所以客户
wanting to kind of pick and choose the
想要选择
capabilities that they use so profiles
他们使用的功能使配置文件
help a little bit and I think actually
有点帮助，我认为实际上
the main way in which profiles help is
配置文件帮助的主要方式是
they give you an understanding of what a
他们使您了解什么是
vendor provides so if a vendor says they
供应商提供，因此如果供应商说他们
support web profile then that's great
支持网站资料，那就太好了
you know that if you're going to that
你知道如果你要去那
vendor they've got all those
供应商，他们拥有所有这些
capabilities as a part of that
能力的一部分
specification you don't necessarily have
您不一定需要的规格
to use them all there are some
使用它们，有一些
environments that provide a number of
提供许多
different profiles that go beyond the
超越了
kind of web profile and full platform
网页个人资料和完整平台
environments so they'll provide cut-down
环境，以便他们提供缩减
examples I guess the most common example
我猜最常见的例子
is Tomcat which is just the kind of
是Tomcat，这只是一种
basic web container capab
基本的Web容器Capab
but then what's been happening over the
但是接下来发生了什么
past few years and we did this in
过去几年，我们在
Webster with Liberty five years ago is
韦伯斯特五年前与自由
some environments are actually giving
实际上有些环境给
the you the ability to pick and choose
您选择的能力
exactly which of the capabilities you
究竟您具有哪些功能
start you want to use so rather than
开始要使用so而不是
thinking of Java EE as a platform when
当将Java EE视为平台时
you have to take the whole thing and
你必须把整个事情
it's potentially bloated and potentially
它可能会肿胀，可能
slow and so on you can start thinking
慢，等等，你可以开始思考
about Java EE as a set of capabilities a
关于Java EE的一系列功能
set of API is and choose which API API
API集，然后选择哪个API API
is you want to use to solve your
你想用来解决你的
particular business problem
特定的业务问题
so with Open Liberty and Webster Liberty
开放自由和韦伯斯特自由
we have this concept of features so as
我们有这种功能的概念
you can see my pointer won't light it up
你可以看到我的指针不会点亮
on the right-hand side this is just an
在右侧，这只是一个
example of a server configuration that's
服务器配置的示例
going to use jax-rs 2.1 and open api 3.0
将使用jax-rs 2.1并打开api 3.0
so you might be in this example doing a
因此您可能在此示例中
rest service and wanting to expose that
休息服务，并希望公开
api out in the form of some document
api以一些文档的形式出现
that can then be used by some consumer
然后可以由某些消费者使用
and then we let you you minify that
然后我们让您将其缩小
server down so it only consists of those
服务器关闭，所以它只包含那些
two those capabilities or any
这两个功能或任何
capabilities of those capabilities
这些能力的能力
depend on so you get a nice constrained
依靠，所以你得到一个很好的约束
package that just fits the fits the
恰好适合的包装
purpose in wildfire wealth ice warm has
目的是在野火财富冰暖有
the it has this fractions concept works
它有这个分数概念作品
slightly differently so it's based off a
略有不同，因此基于
maven dependency declaration so you
Maven的依赖声明，所以你
declare which of the wilds what wildfly
宣布哪个野外是野蝇
swarm fraction you tell I work for IBM
你告诉我我在IBM工作
because I can't say wild fly swarm you
因为我不能说野蝇将你蜂拥而至
pick and choose your wild fly swarm
选择并选择您的野蝇群
fractions based on dependencies and you
基于依赖关系的分数，而您
made an pom and then the build will
做了一个pom，然后构建将
output an executable or runnable jar
输出可执行或可运行的jar
that you can then run that includes
然后可以运行包括
those capabilities so that's the kind of
这些功能，这就是
e aspect and the way we've seen not
方面和我们未曾见过的方式
necessarily as a set of specifications
必须作为一组规范
evolved but how vendors are providing
进化了，但是供应商如何提供
the KDE capabilities that makes it more
KDE功能使它变得更多
appropriate and more suitable to do
合适，更适合做
micro services well then beyond that
微服务远不止于此
there was a kind of feeling that II was
我有种感觉
not evolving as fast as we needed to in
没有像我们需要的那样发展
order to address the requirements for
为了满足以下要求
micro services and so a group of vendors
微服务等一群供应商
got together and formed micro probe
聚在一起形成微探针
i and then sometime later that then
我，然后某个时候
moved to eclipse so there's now the
移到日蚀，所以现在有
Eclipse micro profile project and the
Eclipse微型配置文件项目和
purpose of Eclipse micro profile is
Eclipse微型概要文件的目的是
really to evolve and incubate and an
真正发展和孵化，
experiment with a specifications for in
试用以下规范
in the micro services space so the first
在微服务领域，第一个
one
一
so micro profile 1 0 was was pretty
所以微轮廓1 0很漂亮
basic it just referenced three of the e
基本它只是引用了三个e
specification so it said you're going to
规格，所以它说你要
want to use jax-rs you're going to want
想要使用您想要的jax-rs
to use CDI for injection and you're
使用CDI进行注射，您将
going to want to use JSONP to work with
想要使用JSONP与
Jason and then it created its study
杰森，然后它创建了研究
creating its own own specifications the
创建自己的规范
first one was config which again relates
第一个是配置，这再次与
to what Kate's saying about 12 factor so
凯特说的关于12因子的话
the config spec lets you externalize
配置规范可让您外部化
configuration outside your application
应用程序外部的配置
so you can have this deployable unit you
所以你可以拥有这个可部署的单位
build at the start and as you move
在开始和移动时进行构建
through your pipeline and tested in the
通过您的管道并在
different environments you don't have to
您不必使用不同的环境
rebuild that thing you just change the
重建那件事，你只是改变
configuration as it moves through the
通过时的配置
pipeline fault-tolerance I won't go
我不会去的管道容错
through all of them but I'll pick out
通过所有这些，但我会挑选出来
some of my favorites so fault tolerance
我的一些最爱，所以容错
when you start thinking about assembling
当您开始考虑组装时
applications in terms of a set of
一组应用程序
collaborating services or micro services
协作服务或微服务
then you need to start dealing with
那么你需要开始处理
issues like the fact that there's a
像这样的问题
network involved and the fact that
网络参与和事实
probably another team is responsible for
可能是另一个团队负责
deploying something you that you depend
部署您依赖的东西
on that thing might go away
在那件事上可能会消失
they might upgrade it might fall down on
他们可能会升级，可能会失败
it flat on its face or whatever so fault
它平放在脸上或其他任何故障
tolerance does is define some API some
公差确实是定义一些API
nice annotations that you define the
您定义的漂亮注释
policies that you want to use in order
您要顺序使用的策略
to deal with the potential and
处理潜力和
availability or unreliability of
的可用性或不可靠性
services that you depend on so it
您所依赖的服务
standardizes I think it's like five
标准化，我认为这就像五个
patterns you've got things like bulkhead
像隔板一样的图案
and circuit breaker that's a little
和断路器有点
thank you and also the ability to define
谢谢你，还有定义的能力
a fallback service for example so if you
备用服务，例如，如果您
retry a service five times and you still
重试服务五次，您仍然
don't get a decent answer from it you
没有得到一个体面的答案，你
can go and then call a fallback alright
可以去，然后打电话给后备
so what I'm going to do is just demo
所以我要做的只是演示
God's permitting and do a quick
上帝允许并快速
demo of the the kind of right sizing of
正确尺寸的演示
a server environment so I'm going to use
服务器环境，因此我将使用
open Liberty open limit is an
开放自由开放限制是
open-source app server that we this
我们这的开源应用服务器
isn't my laptop so I'm gonna be pretty
不是我的笔记本电脑，所以我会很漂亮
slow can you all see that no come to the
你们大家能看到很慢吗
front okay I'll talk through it so so we
前面好吧，我会讲讲的，所以我们
what I've done is I've gone to open
我要做的就是打开门
Liberty dot IO and I've downloaded a zip
自由点IO，我已经下载了一个zip
package of the server the zip packages
服务器的软件包zip软件包
76 76 megabytes that includes full java
76 76兆字节，其中包括完整的Java
re' seven capabilities and micro profile
七种功能和微观特征
1.2 capabilities which is latest level
1.2最新功能
of micro profile and the install is just
微型配置文件的安装是
an unzip onto disk so third time lucky
解压缩到磁盘上，所以第三次很幸运
so we've just got this directory here
所以我们在这里有这个目录
that's where the where the servers and
那是服务器和
that and first thing this is the server
那是第一件事，这是服务器
runtime but it's not actually a server
运行时，但实际上不是服务器
instance or any server configuration so
实例或任何服务器配置，因此
the first thing I'm going to do and I
我要做的第一件事就是
need to find the backslash is create a
需要找到反斜杠是创建一个
server ok so I've created a default
服务器确定，所以我创建了一个默认
server and I can I can run that server
服务器，我可以运行该服务器
so I've got the backslash and so as we
所以我有反斜杠
well I don't think I mentioned there's a
好吧，我不认为我提到过
lot of the vendors are focused very put
很多供应商都非常关注
a lot of effort into having quick
付出很多努力
startup of service so for example
服务启动，例如
website Liberty starts in in a few
网站Liberty开始于
seconds a lot of the other other app
其他应用程序的秒数
servers do do so as well so that's the
服务器也这样做，所以
browser I want isn't it
我想要的浏览器不是吗
how you even got the URL ready for me
您甚至如何为我准备好网址
thank you oh we can see it's open
谢谢哦，我们可以看到它已经打开了
Liberty running I've got no apps
自由运行我没有任何应用程序
deployed that's just a kind of default
部署只是一种默认
landing page and so that's running
登陆页面，因此正在运行
running a few capabilities so what I'm
运行一些功能，所以我
going to do is just go into the server
要做的就是进入服务器
directory
目录
and this is where the server
这是服务器
configuration lives and got to remember
配置很重要，请记住
editors we got we've got Visual Studio
编辑器我们拥有Visual Studio
code so if I just edit the server.xml
代码，所以如果我只是编辑server.xml
this is just the default server
这只是默认服务器
configuration now is that going to pop
现在的配置就是弹出
up in that one
在那一个
you've got your fee on running how many
你有多少钱运行多少
yeah okay so you can see the default
是的，所以您可以看到默认
server configuration that we have in
我们拥有的服务器配置
this particular distribution is it's
这个特殊的分布是
going to put JSP in but let's say I just
将要放入JSP，但可以说我只是
want to do the servlets and we'll put
想做小服务程序，我们将把
the version of 3.1 version of servlet
Servlet 3.1版本
and I can save that and you can see on
我可以保存下来，您可以看到
the server side where it's running it
运行它的服务器端
said okay I no longer need JSP 2.3 or
说好吧，我不再需要JSP 2.3或
expression language 3 0 so now I've got
表达式语言3 0所以现在我有了
a server that's just running servlet it
仅运行servlet的服务器
just picked all that up but then I've
刚捡了所有的东西，但是我已经
done my development I built myself an
完成开发工作后，我建立了自己
application and I now want to package
应用程序，我现在要打包
that thing up into a distribution so I'm
那东西放到发行版中，所以我
gonna package the server up and I'm
要打包服务器，我
gonna make it an executable or a
使其成为可执行文件或
runnable jar so I need to specify and
可运行的jar，所以我需要指定和
[Music]
[音乐]
I'm assuming that's a comma
我假设这是一个逗号
okay so as I said at the start of the
好的，正如我在开始时所说的
demo at least the download package is 76
演示至少下载包是76
megabytes
兆字节
I'm now going to package the server up
我现在要打包服务器
and we can see we now got a about 15 and
我们可以看到现在大约有15个
a half Meg server distribution that just
一半的Meg服务器分布
can just run servers and I can run that
可以只运行服务器，我可以运行
thing now so
现在这样
[Music]
[音乐]
and I think just about every vendor
我认为几乎每个供应商
supports runnable jars nowadays but I've
现在支持可运行的罐子，但是我已经
got it later on we'll discuss whether
待会儿我们会讨论是否
and runnable jars are the right thing or
可运行的罐子是对的，或者
not okay and if I go back to the browser
不好，如果我返回浏览器
just refresh that page and yeah you can
只需刷新该页面，是的，您可以
see the server's running so that's just
看到服务器正在运行，这仅仅是
an example and I'll kill that off now so
一个例子，我现在就把它杀死
it doesn't cause us any problems Yeah
不会给我们带来任何麻烦
right back to the slides
马上回到幻灯片
[Music]
[音乐]
well not nothing I've got focus on the
好吧，我没有专心于
slides do I need to do not probably do
我需要做的幻灯片可能不会做
it from the beginning that went yeah
从一开始就行了
yeah so probably to do shift FM function
是的，所以大概要做调频功能
alien keyboard sorry okay
外星人键盘不好意思
so we've seen the kind of alternative
所以我们已经看到了另一种选择
approach to using java re' capabilities
使用Java re功能的方法
now I want to move on on to docker as a
现在我想以
concept so who here is using docker okay
概念，所以这里的人正在使用docker好的
course you probably know more about it
当然您可能对此有更多了解
than I do
比我
who here is doing micro services but not
谁在做微服务，但没有
with docker okay I'd be interested to
和docker好吧，我会对
know what you're using but maybe not
知道你在用什么，但也许不知道
just now so we see a strong correlation
刚才我们看到了很强的相关性
between micro services and docker and
在微服务和docker之间
containers so containers as a concept
容器，所以容器是一个概念
are built on kind of two capabilities
建立在两种功能之上
one is this notion of isolation so that
一个是隔离的概念
you can or namespaces
您可以或名称空间
so that you can avoid flashes of names
这样就可以避免名字的闪烁
of certain things in an environment so
在环境中的某些事物
Linux has this concept of namespaces so
Linux具有名称空间的概念，因此
that you can avoid conflicts on file
这样可以避免文件冲突
system on processes on users and on
系统上的用户和
network and so on so that kind of helps
网络等，这样的帮助
you avoid conflicting on those things
你避免在那些事情上发生冲突
and then it has the concept of control
然后它具有控制的概念
groups or see groups which let you then
组或查看组，然后让您
partition up the resources of the system
划分系统资源
so assigning a certain amount of CPU or
因此分配一定数量的CPU或
a certain amount of memory to a
一定数量的内存
particular container so the the control
特定的容器，因此控件
groups helps avoid the concept of nosy
团体有助于避免爱管闲事的概念
neighbor and if you've heard of that
邻居，如果你听说过
before but know it knows it knows the
之前但知道它知道它知道
noisy neighbor so the name space thing
吵闹的邻居，所以名字空间的事
is the nosy neighbor because you can't
是爱管闲事的邻居，因为你不能
see your neighbors stuff the control
看到你邻居的东西控制
groups is the is noisy neighbor where
组是吵闹的邻居
essentially if you've got a badly
本质上说，如果您患有严重疾病
behaved micro service or something
表现微服务之类的
running on the same host
在同一主机上运行
because you can constrain the resources
因为你可以限制资源
it can use it can't then to up the whole
它可以使用它不能然后整个
system so in the java re' world I think
系统，所以我认为在Java re'世界中
for many years customers have deployed
多年来，客户已经部署
multiple applications to the same
多个应用程序相同
application server instance it's over
应用服务器实例结束
the years it's become a much less common
这些年变得不那么普遍了
pattern because of this noise in a noisy
模式，因为这种噪音在嘈杂
neighbor problem because what would
邻居问题，因为会
happen is they deploy multiple
发生是因为他们部署了多个
applications one application would maybe
一个应用程序可能
have some bad behavior or require more
表现不好或需要更多
resources and you'd end up starving the
资源，您最终会饿死
other applications of resources and
资源的其他应用
causing yourself problems and so let's
造成自己的问题，所以让我们
look at some of the qualities of docker
看一下Docker的一些特质
so what docker provides so docker has
所以码头工人提供的东西
this concept of a docker file the docker
docker文件的概念
file describes what your what when you
文件描述了你什么时候你
build an image what what you want that
建立您想要的图像
image to consist of so in this
在此包含图像
particular example we have already a
一个特殊的例子，我们已经有一个
WebSphere Liberty image that's defined
定义的WebSphere Liberty映像
and we want to add a wall file to it and
我们要向其中添加墙文件
so that will then build another layer a
这样便可以建立另一层
layer another layer on top that includes
在顶部包括另一层
that that war that you can then get an
那场战争，然后你可以得到
image for and then you can then deploy
映像，然后可以进行部署
that as a container so docker gives you
作为一个容器，所以码头工人给你
this kind of consistent way of defining
这种一致的定义方式
that packaging it's also a way that's
包装也是一种方式
independent of Java and the concept of
独立于Java和
micro services is a kind of polyglot
微服务是多语言的
concept you're not going to just
概念你不会只是
necessarily in your organization with
一定在您的组织中
deploying Java you might be deploying
部署您可能要部署的Java
many other types of things so this gives
许多其他类型的事情，所以这给
you a nice way of describing all of
您是描述所有
those things in a consistent way
这些东西以一致的方式
including things like the externals of
包括诸如
the things you're deploying such as what
您正在部署的东西，例如什么
ports do I need to make available that
我需要提供端口
kind of thing I've talked about the the
我谈论过的那种东西
layers what are the nice things about
层次是什么
layers is as you reuse them and build
层是当您重复使用它们并构建时
things on top those those layers can be
那些层之上的东西可以是
cached by the environment so that means
被环境缓存，这意味着
you've got less disk usage because it
您的磁盘使用量较少，因为它
just caches it and you end so there's
只是将其缓存，然后结束，所以
kind of one definition of it that you
那种对你的定义
then build upon unless i/o because
然后建立，除非我/因为
you're not moving because they're cached
你不动，因为他们被缓存
each time you build a new image on top
每次您在顶部建立新图像时
you're not moving those things around
你不会四处走动
you've got a consistent API so docker
你有一个一致的API，所以码头工人
defines things like how you can do
定义诸如您可以做的事情
logging and metrics and volumes and so
日志记录，指标和数量等
on and those things are consistent
那些东西是一致的
across the different types of things
跨越不同类型的事物
that you do you choose to put inside
你选择放入里面
your docker container and the final
您的Docker容器和最终容器
thing is immutability so you can and
事情是不变的，所以你可以和
this again relates to 12 factor you can
这又与12个因素有关
make the thing immutable by essentially
使事物本质上不可变
putting effort into everything in it and
全力以赴
and not referring to things outside
而不是指外面的事情
which means that the contents are not
这意味着内容不
going to behave differently as you move
移动时行为会有所不同
it through your pipeline because they're
它通过您的管道，因为他们是
not relying on things in the external
不依赖外部事物
environment things outside the docker
码头工人以外的环境
container okay so we're going to see
容器好，所以我们要去看看
another demo now and what I'm going to
现在另一个演示，我要去
do is create a project with the IBM
要做的就是与IBM创建一个项目
cloud developer tools CLI which is a
云开发人员工具CLI
mouthful of a name but basically within
满口的名字，但基本上都在
IBM we have several different ways for
IBM我们有几种不同的方式
you to generate a starter project so we
您生成一个入门项目，所以我们
have a CLI you can go in through the IBM
有一个CLI，您可以通过IBM进入
cloud and there's also a websphere
云，还有一个网络圈
liberty source specific page and they
自由源特定页面，它们
all generate a similar application but
都生成类似的应用程序，但是
it just gives you a different entry
它只是给您一个不同的条目
point so I'm going to generate something
点，所以我要产生一些东西
then I'll show building and running with
然后我将展示如何构建和运行
maven and docker and then how you can
Maven和码头工人，然后如何
actually use the mayor and doctorate
实际使用市长和博士学位
environment to keep deploying your
持续部署您的环境
application and Reis without restarting
应用程序和Reis，无需重新启动
the container because if you have to
容器，因为如果您必须
restart your container every time you
每次您重新启动容器
want to see an update then that kind of
想看到一个更新，然后那种
slows down your development time so it's
减慢了您的开发时间，所以
just a nice way to do development so I'm
只是进行开发的好方法，所以我
gonna be running this in a VM because
将在虚拟机中运行，因为
I'm running Windows and I just find
我正在运行Windows，但我发现
docker behaves a little bit better if
码头工人的行为要好一点
I'm running Linux so that's why the demo
我正在运行Linux，所以这就是演示的原因
earlier was running a bit slow because
较早的时候运行有点慢，因为
I've got this VM running in the
我已经在该虚拟机中运行
background so to create a project I
背景，以便创建一个项目我
would run VX dev create so VX dev is the
将运行VX开发人员创建，因此VX开发人员是
CLI tool that I've installed and it
我已安装的CLI工具及其
asking me here if I want to log in to
在这里问我是否要登录
bluemix if I logged in to bluemix which
如果我登录到bluemix，则bluemix
is our IBM cloud then i could get it to
是我们的IBM云，那么我可以将其带到
provision actual services in the cloud
在云中提供实际服务
for me so things like Cloudant or any of
对我来说，像Cloudant之类的东西
our Watson services but for now I'm
我们的Watson服务，但现在我是
going to continue without log
将继续运行而没有日志
and it just won't do any of that
它只是不会做任何事情
provisioning pieces so then goes and
预配件，然后去
retrieves what starters so I can pick my
检索什么启动器，以便我可以选择我的
starting point and here I'm going to
起点，在这里我要
choose that I want a micro service and
选择我想要微服务，
then I have some options of languages so
然后我有一些语言选择
you can see at the top we have I don't
您可以在顶部看到我们没有
if that's big enough hopefully you guys
如果那足够大，希望你们
can see that
可以看到
and but the four options are Java mica
但是四个选项是Java云母
profile Java EE node Python and then a
配置文件Java EE节点Python，然后
Java spring so I'm going to choose micro
Java春天，所以我要选择微型
profile Java EE because that's a topic
对Java EE进行概要分析，因为这是一个主题
of this talk is and then I would name my
这次演讲的内容是
project and create it I can set that off
项目并创建它，我可以将其关闭
going because of the Wi-Fi may or may
由于Wi-Fi可能会或可能会继续
not generate happily so I'm matching a
不能愉快地产生，所以我匹配一个
switch across to one that I created
切换到我创建的一个
earlier while that creates in the
在此之前，
background so I can have a look at the
背景，所以我可以看看
code that I generated earlier and so
我之前生成的代码等等
here it is so when you generate an
这是当您生成一个
application you get a whole bunch of
应用程序，你会得到一大堆
content you get a pom file to build it
内容，您将得到一个pom文件来构建它
you get a docker file to run it docker
您会得到一个docker文件来运行它
you also get some helm shots if you want
如果你愿意的话，你也会得到一些掌舵
to run using helm and some bluemix
使用头盔和一些bluemix运行
specific files if you want to create
如果要创建特定的文件
tool chains and pipelines that deploy to
部署到的工具链和管道
bluemix so you get a whole set of stuff
bluemix，因此您可以获得一整套东西
ready for you to go so to get started I
准备好您可以开始了，我
want might want to build my application
可能想要构建我的应用程序
with envy uninstall so it's set up to
令人羡慕的卸载，所以它设置为
run Liberty in this case that's our Java
在这种情况下运行Liberty是我们的Java
EE micro profile vendor of choice and it
EE微型配置文件首选供应商及其
will build the application then start up
将构建应用程序然后启动
the Liberty server and actually run
Liberty服务器并实际运行
integration tests against the service
针对服务的集成测试
you can see there it's hitting a health
你可以看到那里的健康状况
endpoint to make sure that the apps
端点以确保应用程序
running properly and then it finishes
正常运行，然后完成
building so then I need to build my
建立，然后我需要建立我的
docker container so I've got a docker
码头集装箱，所以我有一个码头工人
file which is just here which we can
文件就在这里，我们可以
have a look at so you can see it's based
看看，所以你可以看到它基于
on a WebSphere Liberty image so
在WebSphere Liberty映像上，因此
WebSphere Liberty has loads of images in
WebSphere Liberty中包含大量图像
your hub that you can check out and then
您可以检查的集线器，然后
we're just copying
我们只是在复制
the content from the server over into
从服务器内容到
the container so if I build that and tag
容器，所以如果我构建它并标记
it with J one demo starts building up my
它与J一个演示开始建立我的
container and as Graham said it's using
容器，正如Graham所说的那样
caching so you can see there it's used
缓存，所以您可以看到它已被使用
cached versions of the application
应用程序的缓存版本
server so it's quite quick for it to
服务器，所以它很快
build cool so that's done so now I can
打造酷，这样就可以了，现在我可以
run my container so I could just run it
运行我的容器，这样我就可以运行它
with a docker run and then it would
与码头工人运行，然后它将
start up and I could access my
启动，我可以访问我的
application and that would all be fine
应用程序，那都很好
but in this instance I'm gonna make some
但在这种情况下，我要做一些
changes to my applications so instead
更改我的应用程序，因此
what I'm going to do is run it with the
我要做的是使用
docker volume so I did a docker run I
码头工人卷，所以我做了一个码头工人我
need to specify port so I'm going to
需要指定端口，所以我要
specify 90-80 as the port and then I'll
指定90-80作为端口，然后我将
specify volume that I want to mount I
指定我要挂载的音量
think my volume is at J one demo and I
认为我的音量在Jone演示上，我
know I've got my server is in my target
知道我的服务器在我的目标内
directory so it's in target Oh Liberty
目录，所以它在目标哦自由
wlp okay actually prints the and WP user
wlp好的，实际上可以打印和WP用户
servers and it's just called default
服务器，它被称为默认
server that's the default server name
服务器是默认服务器名称
that it gets given and then I'm going to
它得到了，然后我要
map it into the config directory so the
将其映射到config目录，以便
config directory is set up for this
为此配置目录
docker container so that you can if you
docker容器，以便您可以
put your config there then the docker
将您的配置放在那里，然后泊坞窗
image for Lib C will just pick up your
Lib C的图片只会接您
config and then I've specified the name
配置，然后我指定了名称
of my container
我的容器
so that will start up the Liberty server
这样就可以启动Liberty服务器
and you can see the logs coming out
你可以看到日志出来了
there and it should pick up the
在那里，它应该拿起
server.xml content that I have in the
我在其中拥有的server.xml内容
target directory so if I show you my
目标目录，所以如果我告诉你我的
target directory quickly in here you can
快速定位目标目录
see that when I did the env and install
看到我做环境并安装时
it put a Liberty here so I have a whole
它在这里放了一个自由，所以我有一个整体
local version of Liberty that installed
安装的本地版本的Liberty
for me and then inside the user servers
对我来说，然后在用户服务器内部
default server directory then I've got
默认服务器目录，然后我有
my config here which you'll see is
我在这里看到的配置是
pretty similar to what Graham was
与格雷厄姆非常相似
showing earlier and if you choose micro
显示较早，如果您选择微型
services then you get the micro profile
服务，那么您会获得微观档案
1o feature which is the Liberty market
自由市场的1o功能
profile feature so my application is now
个人资料功能，因此我的应用程序现在
running and I should be able to access
运行，我应该能够访问
it so if I go to this URL then this
所以如果我去这个URL那么
should tell me whether my application is
应该告诉我我的申请是否
running I get back a health endpoint at
运行时，我在以下位置获得健康终结点
the moment this is just Jason that's
这只是杰森的那一刻
returning but they aim would be that
返回，但他们的目标是
once the micro profile health like
曾经的微轮廓健康
specification is available then we'll
规格可用，我们将
switch to using that I've also got an
切换到使用我也有一个
example endpoint so if I go to v1
端点示例，所以如果我转到v1
example then it says some data has been
然后它说一些数据已经
printed out so then if I go back I can
打印出来，所以如果我回去，我可以
actually update my application so the
实际更新我的应用程序，因此
example is running here and it just says
例子在这里运行，它只是说
some data so I can update this to say
一些数据，所以我可以更新为
hello from one and then I can save that
打个招呼，然后我可以保存
now you can actually set up Liberty
现在您可以实际设置Liberty
within vs code to automatically update
在vs代码中自动更新
but for this demo because I wanted to
但是为了这个演示，因为我想
keep it a little bit vendor agnostic I'm
保持一点供应商不可知我
just going to show running maven and
只是要显示正在运行的Maven，
some of the other vendors have options
其他一些供应商也有选择
where you can actually run maven tasks
您可以在其中实际运行Maven任务
that will then do this update for you
然后将为您执行此更新
and we'll kind of run in the background
我们会在后台运行
so you can see my app from earlier did
这样您就可以看到我以前的应用
get created if I see one CD into this
如果我看到一张CD，就可以创建
one I'm gonna do an MDM package just
我要去做一个MDM包
reproduce the package that I've just
复制我刚才的包
changed so that's going to again compile
更改，以便再次编译
all of my classes and then copy it
我所有的课程，然后将其复制
across and we should see the server on
跨越，我们应该看到服务器在
the left hand side view there it's
左侧视图是
picked up some updates so it found that
获得了一些更新，因此发现
there wasn't a functional update to the
没有功能上的更新
server config but it's noticed that
服务器配置，但注意到
there's been an update to the web
网络上有更新
application and it's dated it there so
应用程序，它在那里过时了
if I go back and do a refresh then you
如果我回去刷新一下，那么你
can see my new message so when you're
可以看到我的新消息，所以当你
then pushing this through the pipeline
然后将其通过管道
you might want to not use a volume and
您可能不希望使用卷
stick with your docker file that is your
坚持使用您的docker文件
one immutable object that you pass
您传递的一个不变的对象
through the pipeline but for developing
通过管道，但用于发展
locally it's nice to be able to not have
在当地很高兴没有
to shut down your docker containers
关闭您的Docker容器
no I didn't rebuild the docker image now
不，我现在没有重建Docker映像
so so all I've done here is I've mounted
所以我在这里所做的就是安装
a volume into the docker container so
卷到Docker容器中
rather than it using the copy the copy
而不是使用副本
of my config that got copied in by the
我的配置被复制的
docker file it's actually using the
docker文件，它实际上是在使用
location that I mounted so when I did
我安装的位置，所以当我做
the MDM package it would have been
原来的MDM包
updated in there and actually if I'd
在那里更新，实际上如果我愿意
have used their built-in support in that
使用了内置的支持
we have in vs code for liberty or we
我们在vs代码中获得自由，或者
have tools in Eclipse as well then I
在Eclipse中也有工具
could have actually set up so that I
本来可以设置的，以便我
could just change the class save it and
可以只更改类保存它，然后
it would have automatically updated for
它会自动更新为
me yes so it's my container is picking
我是的所以这是我的容器在捡
up when I did the MV and install I got
当我做MV并安装时
an updated application in this folder
此文件夹中已更新的应用程序
down here in my drop ins folder and
在我的drop ins文件夹中，
that's what it's picking up so I mounted
那就是它的拾取，所以我安装了
this whole directory the soda pop
苏打汽水整个目录
default server directory here that's
这是默认服务器目录
what I'm out it so that's what happened
我在外面出来的就是这样
when I did
当我做
and package your copied in there and
并将您复制的文件打包在那里
then the update happened well so I think
然后更新进行得很好，所以我认为
that's all I wanted to demo from that
这就是我要演示的全部
point of view I'm gonna stop the docker
的观点，我要停止码头工人
container because that will slow things
容器，因为这会减慢速度
down
下
and that leads onto the next so so this
然后通向下一个
is the demo that I just did will if we
如果我们做的是我刚才做的演示
haven't like answered your question at
不喜欢在回答您的问题
the end then ask it again but hopefully
最后再问一次，但希望
this should answer people think you're a
这应该回答人们以为你是一个
plantain we're just going to ask that
车前草，我们只是要问
just to the right time
恰到好处的时间
okay so packaging so when you're
好吧，所以包装，当你
considering the packaging for your micro
考虑您的微型包装
services there are a number of
服务有很多
characteristics that you might want to
您可能想要的特征
kind of ask yourselves what do I want to
问自己我想做什么
achieve from my packaging do I want it
从我的包装中实现我想要吗
to be externally configurable because I
可以在外部配置，因为我
want to kind of follow the twelve factor
想要跟随十二个因素
practices do I want it to be immutable
我希望它是一成不变的
again relating to twelve factors so I
再次与十二个因素有关，所以我
can be confident that the thing that I
可以相信我的事
built at the start and run my unit tests
一开始就构建并运行我的单元测试
against is the same thing that I'm going
我要反对的是同一件事
to test maybe in my staging environment
在我的暂存环境中进行测试
maintainable we all want maintainability
可维护的我们都希望可维护性
don't we and the choices that you make
我们和您所做的选择
in terms of packaging may may be it may
在包装方面可能是可能
affect the main factor maintainability
影响主要因素的可维护性
of your your micro-service consistent so
您的微服务始终如一
do you want consistency may be across
你想保持一致性吗
microservices so you deploy many many
微服务，因此您可以部署许多
micro services consistency can help in
微服务一致性可以帮助
terms of people wanting to move move
人们想搬家的条件
teams and work on different micro
团队和从事不同的微工作
services and so on maximizing reuse and
服务等，以最大程度地重用
sharing again the approach you take can
再次分享您采用的方法
help maximize reuse and sharing do you
帮助您最大程度地重复利用和共享
want separation between what you build
想要分离您构建的内容
as a team or as a squad in terms of the
作为一个团队或一个小队
application code and what you're reusing
应用程序代码以及您要重用的内容
which might be a vendor's java
这可能是供应商的Java
environment or it might be some open
环境，或者可能是开放的
source frameworks that you're adding
您要添加的源框架
into the environment having that kind of
进入那种环境
separation can be important and then one
分离可能很重要，然后一个
of the kind of quite often the elephant
像大象一样
in the room is the organizational fit I
在房间里适合我
work with a lot of big customers who
与许多大客户合作
have separate dev teams separate op
有独立的开发团队独立的运营
teams and hands up if that's that's the
团队和举起手来，如果那是
environment you work in yeah yeah so the
你在这里工作的环境是的，所以
opportunist and a PI server that's what
机会主义者和PI Server是什么
they've done for years they own that
他们已经做了很多年了
they're responsible for that and that's
他们对此负责
great and the dev team of historically
伟大而历史悠久的开发团队
thrown a war file over the wall with
向墙上扔一个战争文件
some configuration or whatever and said
一些配置或什么说
do that for me and now the dev team is
为我做到这一点，现在开发团队是
going I'm doing micro-services I'm going
我正在做微服务
to give you an Apple jar and they go
给你一个苹果罐，他们去
what do I do with that so that's an
我该怎么办，所以
important consideration because
重要的考虑，因为
organizational change is quite quite
组织变革相当
often a lot harder than technological
通常比技术难得多
change okay so we talked about
改变好了，所以我们谈到了
yup servers and how the ability to
yup服务器以及如何
customize your runtime environments
自定义您的运行时环境
we've talked we've seen examples of
我们已经谈过，我们看到了一些例子
runnable jars and we talked about
可运行的罐子，我们谈到了
containers so what's the best choice
容器，什么是最好的选择
what's the best fit and it can kind of
什么是最合适的，它可以
depend so if you're using docker and
因此，如果您使用的是docker和
particularly if you're a polyglot
特别是如果你是一个会说多种语言的人
environment we're deploying multiple
我们正在部署多个环境
things then then you're going to want to
事情然后你会想要
use docker as your packing Packaging
使用docker作为包装
mechanism and the thing is once you're
机制，事情是一旦你
doing docker then you probably want to
做码头工人，那么你可能想
benefit from all the docker capabilities
受益于所有docker功能
so what we talked about in terms of the
所以我们谈论的是
layers and the images and the the
层和图像以及
caching and so on so think about
缓存等等，所以考虑一下
structuring them I can see it think
构建他们，我可以看到它的想法
about structuring your environment in
关于在
terms of the kind of based operating
基础操作的种类
system putting Java down putting your
系统将Java放下
server down and then there might be
服务器关闭，然后可能有
frameworks and libraries that are they
它们是框架和库
reusing open in open source or maybe
在开源中重复使用开源，或者
you're a developed in-house and you
你是一个内部开发的人
might want to put those in as a in as a
可能希望将它们作为一个
layer because putting them in there
层，因为将它们放在那里
makes them explicit you know which of
让他们明确你知道哪个
your docker containers are then using
然后您的Docker容器正在使用
those things and if you've got a
这些东西，如果你有一个
security vulnerability or you need to
安全漏洞，或者您需要
upgrade something you think you can see
升级您认为可以看到的内容
quite easily what your dependencies are
很容易你的依赖是什么
and where you need to maybe do a
而你可能需要做一个
redeploy or rebuild and redeploy of a
重新部署或重建和重新部署
particular micro service and then
特定的微服务，然后
finally add your application thing in so
最终在其中添加您的应用程序
as you go down that stack hopefully the
希望您沿着那个栈走下去时
things very less often the things at the
事情很少发生
top of the things are going to change
最重要的事情将会改变
the most which is your application code
最重要的是您的应用程序代码
and if you're doing runnable jars then
如果你在做可运行的罐子
and you get I think less flexibility and
而且我认为您的灵活性降低了，
also it doesn't work particularly work
也没有用，特别是工作
very well for a polyglot environment
非常适合多语言环境
however if even if you're using docker
但是，即使您正在使用docker
as I mentioned about the organizational
正如我提到的组织
aspect of it you might not be the person
你可能不是那个人
that creates the docker image that might
创建可能会
be our ops team in which case war again
成为我们的行动团队，在这种情况下又会发生战争
is probably the best thing for you as a
对你来说可能是最好的事情
development team to create as a package
开发团队以打包方式创建
and then you give it to the ops team and
然后将其交给操作团队
then there you go and do the docker
然后你去做码头工人
things things with that rather than
事情，而不是那个
giving them an executable jar which
给他们一个可执行的jar
they've then got to go and look inside
然后他们必须去里面看
and try and find your war file and pull
并尝试找到您的战争档案并拉
it out and go and put it inside the
拿出来放进去
docker container okay so the last thing
码头集装箱好了，所以最后一件事
we want to talk about here to say is the
我们想在这里说的是
open API specification so those of you
开放的API规范，让您
who aren't aware it's a simple standard
谁不知道这是一个简单的标准
API description format version 2 was
API说明格式第2版原为
released back in October 2014 and back
发布于2014年10月
then it was the from swagger and then
然后是从招摇，然后
now version 3 is the open API
现在版本3是开放的API
specification so the swagger kind of
规格，所以招摇
specification was well
规格很好
swag was donated as part of the open API
赃物作为开放API的一部分捐赠
specification and there are some
规格，还有一些
different implementations so I've
不同的实现方式
mentioned swagger there and often people
提到那里大摇大摆，经常有人
use swagger and open API as
使用招摇和开放的API作为
interchangeable words and you can find a
可互换的单词，你可以找到一个
lot of vendors actually support this as
许多供应商实际上都支持
part of their application server say for
他们的应用服务器的一部分说
example with Liberty we have a feature
自由的例子，我们有一个功能
that's that provides it and again with
那就是提供它，并再次
wild fly swarm they have a fraction that
野蝇群中有一部分
provides it why is this useful for micro
提供了为什么这对微型有用
services well for micro services
微服务的服务很好
communication between the services is
服务之间的通信是
really a key aspect that you need to get
确实是您需要获得的关键方面
right because you're suddenly in a
对，因为你突然陷入
distributed system you need to have good
分布式系统需要具备良好的
communication between those different
那些不同的人之间的交流
parts and along with micro services
零件以及微服务
often comes an organizational change
通常会发生组织变革
where you have different teams that own
您拥有不同的团队
the different micro services from sort
不同的微服务
of writing the code all the way up to
一直编写代码的过程
deploying and support and that means
部署和支持，这意味着
that you need a well documented API
您需要一个有据可查的API
between the different micro services so
在不同的微服务之间
the open API specification comes in very
开放的API规范非常有用
well here and it can be used in testing
好在这里，它可以用于测试
specifically to make sure that both the
特别是要确保
producer and consumer of a particular
特定生产者和消费者
API is keeping too
API也保持
the specification that you have chosen
您选择的规格
and there are a set of different tools
有一套不同的工具
that you can use one such tool is
您可以使用一种这样的工具是
something called pact where you can
所谓的契约
define tests that can be run by the
定义可以由
people producing the API to make sure
人们生产API以确保
that they haven't regressed anything or
他们没有退缩任何东西，或者
changed anything that would break their
改变了任何会破坏他们的东西
consumers another thing to think about
消费者要考虑的另一件事
it's micro-services driven by desire for
它是由对微服务的渴望驱动的
short life cycles so rather than having
生命周期短，所以没有
one big application that started being
一个大的应用程序开始
written a long time ago and you just
很久以前写的
keep adding pieces on the edge you're
继续在自己的边缘添加片段
likely to be writing new applications
可能正在编写新的应用程序
much more frequently and with that it's
更频繁的是
useful to be able to have some
能够有一些有用的
auto-generated code so I already
自动生成的代码，所以我已经
demonstrated today how we generate an
今天演示了我们如何产生
application but actually being able to
应用程序，但实际上能够
generate based off a API dess
基于API dess生成
specification is very useful and that's
规范非常有用，那就是
where open API documentation can be used
可以使用开放API文档的地方
it's also polyglot and a multi-vendor
它也是多语言和多供应商
environment so you can use open API even
环境，因此您甚至可以使用开放式API
if you're micro services made up of
如果您是由微服务组成的
services that are all in different
不同的服务
languages so for myself when I've been
语言对我自己来说
working with my colleagues who have
与我的同事一起工作
microsomes that need to interact with
需要与之相互作用的微粒体
mine even if there's a written in say
我的，即使有一个书面的说
JavaScript or Python or whatever we can
JavaScript或Python或其他我们可以
all have this one view of how they
所有人对他们如何有这种看法
should interact so I mentioned code
应该互动，所以我提到了代码
generation there's a lot of open source
一代有很多开源
tools available if you go look on maven
如果您去看Maven，可以使用的工具
for example there's a whole set that you
例如，有一整套你
can use and some of the vendors actually
可以使用，实际上一些供应商
supply like built-in support for you to
像内置支持一样为您提供
generate code based on specifications or
根据规范生成代码或
generate the actual document to show the
生成实际文档以显示
specification of your API based on the
基于的API规范
code so you can go both ways so in the
代码，因此您可以同时使用两种方式
IBM cloud we have an option for you to
IBM cloud我们为您提供了一个选择
generate an application given the
给定生成一个应用程序
document and we also provide this from
文件，我们也提供
the Liberty app accelerator which I
我的自由应用加速器
mentioned earlier so you can see the
前面提到过，所以你可以看到
swagger button there in the corner and
角落里有招摇按钮
the wildfly swarm project generator
Wildfly群项目生成器
which is sort of their equivalent to the
这相当于它们的
app accelerator also provides this
应用加速器还提供了
option and so here's a quick sort of
选项，这是一种快速的选择
diagram in case you're not aware of what
图，以防您不知道什么
it might look like if you were going to
如果您要
use this technology so you can have your
使用这项技术，以便您拥有
actual endpoint specified in similar way
以类似方式指定实际端点
that you would with just Chuck's or s
与Chuck或s一样
and then you can add extra sort of user
然后您可以添加其他类型的用户
information as well with swagger and the
信息以及招摇和
nice thing is it produced s-- it
好东西是它产生的
produces this UI so I've used this a lot
产生这个UI，所以我已经用了很多
when doing development because you can
在进行开发时，因为您可以
it's a nice way to visualize the API and
这是可视化API和
get a real understanding for what the
真正了解什么
team want out of the API and how you
团队想要退出API，以及您如何
might interact with it and so for
可能会与之互动，因此
example with Liberty if you use their
使用Liberty的示例
API discovery feature then you'll get
API发现功能，您将获得
this you are as part of that so in
这是你的一部分，所以在
conclusion we think you should consider
结论我们认为您应该考虑
the individual capabilities of Java EE
Java EE的个别功能
it isn't something that you have to take
这不是你必须采取的
as one big lump you can choose the
作为一大块，您可以选择
different pieces that you want and make
您想要和制作的不同作品
it the right fit for you you should
它最适合您，您应该
choose your runtime to fit the
选择适合您的运行时
particular capabilities that you require
您需要的特定功能
and different vendors provide different
和不同的供应商提供不同的
options for how you can do this with
如何使用此功能的选项
docker as the packaging model jar files
docker作为打包模型jar文件
maybe isn't something that is useful and
也许不是有用的东西，
actually you can just stick with a wor
其实你可以坚持
phone but again it depends exactly what
手机，但又要取决于什么
you're doing but having talked or
你在做但在说话或
something's in your environment will
您环境中的某些东西会
definitely be useful for micro services
绝对对微服务有用
and then of course the Mike profile
然后是Mike的个人资料
community adds programming model
社区增​​加了编程模型
essentials and removes boilerplate that
要点并删除样板
you would otherwise have had to read to
否则您将不得不阅读
write so it provides annotations and
写，以便它提供注释和
things to get your micro service written
编写微服务的东西
more quickly and sort of the code more
更快，代码更多
clean finally we've got the swagger or
清洁最后我们大摇大摆或
open API specification which you can
您可以打开API规范
make use of as part of Java EE the
用作Java EE的一部分
different vendors support it and then it
不同的供应商支持它，然后它
can be used even if you're we've got a
即使您有一个也可以使用
polyglot environment so we've got a few
多语言环境，所以我们有一些
resources here if you want to go read
如果您想阅读这里的资源
more about micro services and there's a
有关微服务的更多信息，还有一个
red book which I actually co-wrote with
我实际上与他合写的红皮书
some colleagues of mine and that kind of
我的一些同事和那种
gives a general overview for Java but
给出了Java的一般概述，但
it's got some Java EE specifics in it as
它里面有一些Java EE细节
well whereas dev dotnet is the WebSphere
好，而dev dotnet是WebSphere
Liberty developer site so all the
Liberty开发人员网站
developers myself and Gro included that
开发人员本人和Gro包括
work on Liberty have written articles up
关于自由的工作已经写了文章
there and documents about micro services
那里以及有关微服务的文件
and then you can also go to micro
然后你也可以去微
service builder which is the sort of
服务构建者
Liberty and IBM cloud private version of
Liberty和IBM Cloud私有版本
the bxf tools that I showed you and then
我向您展示的bxf工具，然后
of course we've got links to open
当然，我们有打开链接
Liberty
自由
which we've recently announced and Reiko
我们最近宣布了和玲子
profile ire and if you want some reading
个人资料生气，如果您想阅读
then we've got some resources for you to
那么我们有一些资源供您
check out as well so I think that's
还要检查一下，所以我认为
about all we have time for thank you
差不多我们有时间要谢谢你
very much for coming and we welcome any
非常欢迎光临，我们欢迎任何
questions
问题
[Applause]
[掌声]